britmums.com 2019-07-06

# BritMums Privacy Policy - BritMums

This policy explains the way that we collect, use and protect your data as well as your options with regard to your data.

We’ve tried to be as clear as possible, avoiding unnecessary jargon, while including all the relevant information. Please do email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#7f161119103f1d0d160b120a120c511c1012) if something doesn’t make sense or needs expanding. 

### Our duty of care

We recognise our duty of care with regards to your data and will always endeavour to do the right thing with the personal data you choose to share with us, including: not compromising your anonymity; protecting your privacy; storing your data securely, giving you control over your own data and never selling your information.

We believe that employing data and data analytics appropriately can improve the user experience on the BritMums websites and network. Data you give us when filling in forms (when joining the [BritMums Network](http://community.britmums.com/) and/or the [BritMums Pro group](http://pro.britmums.com/), for example, or when using the site) helps us show you more relevant content and offer you more targeted opportunities to work with us and with brands. It also allows us to see which aspects of the site are popular and well-used, meaning we can improve BritMums for everyone.

### How to get in touch

Our registered office address and where you can ‘snail mail’ us is:

Chiltern Home Business Centre

Chiltern House, 45 Station Road

Henley-on-Thames Oxfordshire RG9 1AT

Email enquiries should got to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#ff96919990bfbd8d968bb28a928cd19c9092 "info@BritMums.com").

### About the Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy sets out how BritMums uses any information that you give when you use this website or any services which we provide. If you do not agree to this policy, do not use this website, the BritMums Network or the BritMums Pro group.

Your enjoyment in being part of the BritMums Network is important to us. We want to make it as easy and simple as possible. As part of the operation of BritMums, we gather certain types of information about our members, and we would like to explain the types of information we gather, what we do with it and how to correct or change the information.

### Personal Information

Personal data is collected such as your email address when you become a member of the BritMums Network and also when you engage with our Sites and this Blog, to make a post for example.

We will use the information you provide to enable your use of Services available on the BritMums Network, BritMums Pro and the Blog, to contact you personally if necessary for the provision of the services available on the Network, BritMums Pro and the Blog, and to keep track of who uploads/ posts. **We will never under any circumstances sell your Personal Data.** The information is used to make your time spent on the BritMums area and the Blog more enjoyable, improve the content of the Sites and Blog, to customize the content and/or layout of the Site for each individual user and to notify users about updates to the Site or Blog or promotional offers or opportunities that we believe will be of interest to you.

Please note that if you post contact details online that are accessible to the public you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

### BritMums Pro

When you join BritMums Pro and apply for BritMums projects you provide additional information about yourself. This information is used solely for BritMums Pro projects. The information is held using third-party providers who themselves also adhere to GDPR regulations.  

### Aggregated Information

Aggregated information, such as which pages users access or visit and information volunteered by users, such as survey information and/or site registrations, is collected through various methods. For example, the sites log IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that “serve up” Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a page from any site, our servers log your IP address

### Cookies and Tracking Devices

BritMums may use cookies or other tracking devices. Cookies do not allow the website to access personal information that you have not already provided. You can refuse to use cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use most of BritMums Site and the Blog. However, you may find that some areas on the Site will be slower, or may not function at all.

For more information about cookies, please visit [this page](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) on Wikipedia.

### Children under the age of 13

Because BritMums is not intended for children under the age of 13, we do not provide memberships or registration to persons under age 13. Prospective users may not sign up for any aspect of the network site, and are not eligible to enter any of our promotions. Except as may be required by law, we will not knowingly collect, maintain, or disclose any personal information from children under the age of 13.

### Children between the ages of 13 and 18

BritMums is similarly not intended for persons under the age of 18. If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, please let your parent or guardian know if you are spending time at BritMums or the BritMums Blog. Also share this Privacy Policy with them and get their permission. Do not post your real name on a web site or message board, and never tell anyone online anything private about yourself or your family, including your phone number and address.

### Additional Information

BritMums may contain links to other sites that you may access. These other sites should have their own privacy policies and you should review those policies. We cannot control the information disclosed at these third-party sites or how that information is used.

No transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under our control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk.

### USE OF THIS SITE AND OTHER BRITMUMS SITES SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

The issue of privacy is an evolving one. BritMums committed to the constant monitoring and examination of our privacy practices, and may, from time to time, institute changes to our Privacy Policy. In the event that any material changes are made to our privacy practices, we will promptly make changes to this Privacy Policy that reflect such changes; therefore we recommend you review our policy regularly to check for updates. You can send e-mail to us with any further questions at the email address at the beginning of this Privacy Policy.

Should you have questions or wish to access the personal information we retain about you please email us [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#6c05020a032c2e1e05182119011f420f0301).
